rollins.edu 2017-12-17

# Privacy Policy | The Fine Print | Rollins College | Winter Park, FL

At Rollins College, we collect and manage user data according to the following Privacy Policy, with the goal of incorporating our organization's mission of educating students for global citizenship and responsible leadership, empowering graduates to pursue meaningful lives and productive careers. We are committed to the liberal arts ethos and guided by its values and ideals. Our guiding principles are excellence, innovation, and community. This document is part of Rollins College's Terms of Service, and by using Rollins.edu (the “Website”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. Please read the Terms of Service in their entirety, and refer to those for definitions and contacts.

## Data Collected

We collect anonymous data from every visitor of the Website to monitor traffic and fix bugs. For example, we collect information like web requests, the data sent in response to such requests, the Internet Protocol address, the browser type, the browser language, and a timestamp for the request.

## Use of the Data

We only use your personal information to provide you requested services or to communicate with you about the services or the Website.

With respect to any personal information you may choose to upload to Rollins.edu, we take the privacy and confidentiality of such documents seriously. We encrypt all confidential information, and we adhere to strict rules regarding storage of that information (please see Rollins College Policy for the Preservation of Electronically Stored Information for more information).

We employ industry standard techniques to protect against unauthorized access of data about you that we store, including personal information.

We do not share personal information you have provided to us without your consent, unless:

  * doing so is appropriate to carry out your own request;
  * we believe it's needed to enforce our Terms of Service, or that is legally required;
  * we believe it's needed to detect, prevent or address fraud, security or technical issues;
  * otherwise protect our property, legal rights, or that of others.

Rollins.edu is operated from the United States. If you are visiting the Website from outside the U.S., you agree to any processing of any personal information you provide us according to this policy.

Rollins College and its representatives may contact you, by email or other means. For example, Rollins College may send you promotional emails relating to topics you have requested information on, or communicate with you about your use of the Rollins.edu website. Rollins College may also use technology to alert us via a confirmation email when you open an email from us. You can modify your email notification preferences by clicking the appropriate link included in the footer of email notifications. If you do not want to receive promotional email from Rollins College, please opt out of receiving emails at the bottom of any Rollins College emails or by editing your profile preferences. Rollins College uses multiple methods of emailing information to its constituents, so it may be necessary to opt-out more than once.

## Sharing of Data

We don't share your personal information with third parties. Only aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Rollins.edu Website and service. We currently use Google Analytics (traffic analysis, SEO optimization), multiple email management systems such as Mailchimp and Constant Conact, and other systems. We listed below what data these third parties extract exactly. Feel free to check out their own Privacy Policies to find out more.

  * Google Analytics: anonymous (ad serving domains, browser type, demographics, language settings, page views, time/date), pseudonymous (IP address)
  * Email management systems: name and email of our subscription list

We also use social buttons provided by services like Twitter, Google+, LinkedIn and Facebook. Your use of these third party services is entirely optional. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these third party services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those third party services’ privacy policies.

We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our “Agents”). We may need to share personal information with our Agents in order to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make major changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Website or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

Should you have any question or concern, please write to [websupport@rollins.edu](mailto:websupport@rollins.edu).
